[{"id": 2921, "question": "British MPs have voted in favour of the creation of babies with DNA from two women and one man, in a historic move. The UK is now set to become the first country to introduce laws to allow the creation of babies from three people. In a free vote in the Commons, 382 MPs were in favour and 128 against the technique that stops genetic diseases being passed from mother to child. During the debate, ministers said the technique was \"light at the end of a dark tunnel\" for families. A further vote is required in the House of Lords. If everything goes ahead then the first such baby could be born next year. Supporters said it was \"good news for progressive medicine\" but critics say they will continue to fight against the technique that they say raises too many ethical and safety concerns. Estimates ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following statements is NOT true?", "options": ["The new technique is intended to provide the parents a healthy baby.", "The mitochondrial disease can lead to various fatal illnesses.", "Britain is the first country to have created three-person babies.", "All of Ms Bernadi's children died of a genetic disease."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 69, "question": "School is out for the summer in some areas, and for many children, that means weeks of sleeping in late, trips to the swimming pool or hours spent in front of the TV. These months of inactivity--- away from the daily tiring things of school--- are something that young people look forward to, but it can have a detrimental influence on the knowledge they have. Studies have shown that children lose a lot in math skills during the summer months. Children who spend little time learning experience a much greater amount of learning loss than those who often take part in summer programs. So when school starts again in the fall, teachers often have to spend several weeks reteaching children material that they have forgotten. Experts suggest that parents make sure the summer months are a time of con...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true?", "options": ["It isn't good for children to have fun in summer.", "Children will get bored with reading programs", "Summer programs can be helpful for children.", "Teachers needn't help children review lessons."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1827, "question": "September is an exciting month in every college freshman's life. For many, it's the first time that they've left home to live in a new environment. But after the hustle and bustle of a few weeks, excitement gives way to a less enjoyable emotion-- homesickness. Homesickness manifests itself in many ways. You may miss mum's cooking, your pets, or even your old bed. All this becomes a fond memory of the past. Homesickness can be a bitter feeling for many students, especially when faced with the challenges of settling into an unfamiliar environment. But remember, you're not alone. According to a recent BBC article, 70 percent of British college students experience homesickness. In this increasingly globalized world in which people migrate to faraway places for a relationship, education or work...\n\nQ: According to the passage, we can know that   _  .", "options": ["homesickness may cause mental diseases", "homesickness is a feeling only shared by adults", "homesickness won't do any good to our health", "homesickness is also called nostalgia in Switzerland"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3245, "question": "Italy is one country where beauty is prized more than any other virtue. That is, except in the small town of Piobbico, the self-declared World Capital of Ugly People. The road sign at the edge of the town even warns visitors that they are entering the ugly zone. People who consider themselves ugly have been gathering in Piobbico since the 1960s. That's when Ugly Club president Telesforo Lacobelli established a dating agency for women who believed they were too ugly to attract husbands. Lacobelli believes that he is ugly himself because he has a short nose in a country where long or large noses have always been considered beautiful. People from around the world travel to Piobbico to tell their sad stories of ugliness. During the annual Festival of the Ugly, which occurs on the first Sunday ...\n\nQ: Piobbico is rather special in that  _  .", "options": ["it is a very small town", "it is home to ugly people", "it receives no visitors", "it is the capital of Italy"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3042, "question": "Welcome to Gold Coast Wax Museum HIGHLIGHTS The Gold Wax Museum is one of the Cold Coast's longest running attractions. It's a collection of famous figures. It's Australia's largest museum of its kind, featuring more than 110 life-size wax figures copies of British and Australian History. The Wax Museum is visited by many thousands of people each year who are shocked at the amazing realism of the life-size figures in authentic costumes. This is your invitation to wander through at your leisure and meet many important and famous people's figures on Queensland's Gold Coast. Come face to face with such celebrities as Michael Jackson, President Obama, past President John F. Kennedy, King Hussein, members of the Royal Family, and many others whose lives have all left an indelible mark on our wo...\n\nQ: You will most probably find this passage   _  .", "options": ["in a guidebook", "in a magazine", "in a text book", "on a webpage"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1119, "question": "\"Migrant workers\" is a familiar term for 17-year-old Shi Jian. Her father and uncle often talk about the problems surrounding this group of people. However, Shi cares more about the children of these migrant workers. Last year Shi's housekeeper's daughter had to give up her schooling in Beijing because she would not be allowed to sit the national college entrance exam. She was forced to continue her high school education in her hometown in Sichuan Province. Shi thinks the current law is unfair for migrant workers' children, as it prevents them from studying at public schools, unless their parents pay huge sums. So, Shi decided to do a survey of migrant workers so that she could find some solutions to help solve the problem. In the last six months Shi spoke to 186 migrant workers in Beijing...\n\nQ: Shi suggested in her survey that   _", "options": ["more private schools for migrants' children should be built", "more money should be collected for migrants' children", "children's tuition should be reduced", "students from the city and the countryside should be encouraged to communicate more"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2236, "question": "A new international study shows that some people's biological clock plays a powerful role for their life expectancy, regardless of lifestyle choices. Published in the latest issue ofAgingon Wednesday, the study has found the most definitive evidence to explain why some people keep healthy lifestyle but die younger than others. Geneticist Steve Horvath from the University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), led a team of 65 scientists around the world to record age-related changes to human DNA, analyse blood samples collected from 13, 000 people and estimate their lifespan. A higher biological age, regardless of actual age, consistently predicts an earlier death, the study says. \"You get people who are vegan, sleep 10 hours a day, have a low-stress job, and still end up dying young,\" Horvath...\n\nQ: Which of the following would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["We all should keep healthy lifestyle", "Geneticist finds anti-aging interventions", "Biological clock predicts life expectancy", "Horvath builds an important milestone"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1388, "question": "Many years ago, when I was fresh out of school and working in Denver, I was driving to my parents' home in Missouri for Christmas. I stopped at a gas station about 50 miles from Oklahoma City, where I was planning to stop and visit a friend. While I was standing in line at the cash register , I said hello to an older couple who were also paying for gas. I took off, but had gone only a few miles when black smoke poured from the back of my car. I stopped and wondered what I should do. A car pulled up behind me. It was the couple I had spoken to at the gas station. They said they would take me to my friend's We chatted on the way into the city, and when I got out of the car, the husband gave me his business card. I wrote him and his wife a thank-you note for helping me. Soon afterward, I rece...\n\nQ: The battery of the author's car was dead because  _  .", "options": ["something went wrong with the lights", "the meeting lasted a whole day", "he forgot to turn off the lights", "he drove too long a distance"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 795, "question": "When I opened my e-mail the other day, a pretty woman named Rachel appeared on my computer screen. She greeted me by name and started talking with great enthusiasm . Every now and then she stopped to smile at me or blow a kiss. She was reading to me an e-mail from my brother, and a lot of it was about the trouble he had getting the phone company to give him a high-speed Internet connection. It was pretty cool. Rachel was there thanks to a new technology called Facemail. An ace man lets you send an e-mail that gets ready to the recipient by an attractive male or female from or by a clown . The software, which is free, can be downloaded at www.facemail.com. Facemail faces are lifelike, and they simulate emotions based on emotions-for example, that you put in your text. Type in; -x, and Rache...\n\nQ: The main advantage of Facemail is that_.", "options": ["you can see the person who sends you the email", "you can put your own emotions in the email", "e-mail can be read in a more lovely way", "you can hire a beautiful woman to read the email to you"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 292, "question": "The Queen's English is now sounding less upper-class, a scientific study of the Queen's Christmas broadcasts has found. Researchers have studied each of her messages to the Commonwealth countries since 1952 to find out the change in her pronunciation from the noble Upper Received to the Standard Received. Jonathan Harrington, a professor at Germany's University of Munich, wanted to discover whether accent changes recorded over the past half century would take place within one person. \"As far as I know, there just is nobody else for whom there is this sort of broadcast records,\" he said. He said the noble way of pronouncing vowels had gradually lost ground as the noble upper-class accent over the past years. \"Her accent sounds slightly less noble than it did 50 years ago. But these are very...\n\nQ: We may infer from the text that the Journal of Phonetics is a magazine on  _  .", "options": ["Christmas customs", "speech sounds", "TV broadcasting", "personal messages"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2926, "question": "Steps Shoes Salon Steps Shoes Salon, 4518 S.Cottage Grove, knows our \"economy is weathering a little storm\" They've discounted winter botts and shoes for their fellow shoes lovers.So step in and save! Hours: 11a.m.to 7 p.m.Monday through Friday; 11 a.m.to 6 p.m.Saturaday; Noon to 5 p.m.the first Sunday of this month (closeed other Sundays).Call 773-548 Jonathan Saunders for Target If you've ever watched a runway shoes and thought \"yeah, that dress would be awesome if it wasn't $ 1,800\", you'll be very pleased to know that British designer Jonathan Saunders has decided to use his powers for good and offer fashion - forward clothing.His collection was inspired by the works of Gustav Klimt, Jackson Pollack and Rothko.The clothing ranges from $ 14.99 to $ 29.99 and is only available until Nove...\n\nQ: What can we learn about Jonathan Saunders from the passage?", "options": ["Most of his designs are classical.", "The clothes he designed are affordable.", "He is returning to Britain on November 1.", "Rothko once instructed him in designing."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2224, "question": "While many other teen stars built up their celebrity status by working hard on popular TV shows, Justin shot straight to the top by using social media. A few years ago, Justin uploaded videos of himself on YouTube, showing _ of his favorite songs at home. He just saw it as a bit of fun for friends and family, but when music manager Scooter Braun saw one of the videos, he flew to Justin's hometown of Ontario, Canada to sign him up. Justin was just 13. Shortly after, Justin was flown to the US. He eventually started working with R&B superstar Usher. Justin's first album My world was released in 2009. But all the time, Justin continued to build his fan base on his YouTube account, where some of his original home videos can still be found, and where he continues to post music. \"I wasn't sendin...\n\nQ: Which one is right according to the passage?", "options": ["Justin posted videos online in order to succeed.", "Justin becomes a celebrity partly owing to social media.", "Justin has the same way to succeed as others.", "Justin has built many websites."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1427, "question": "Money spent on advertising is money spent as well as any I know of.It serves directly to assist a rapid distribution of goods at reasonable prices, thereby establishing a firm home market and so making it possible to provide for export at competitive prices.By drawing attention to new ideas it helps enormously to raise standards of living.By helping to increase demand it ensures an increased need for labour, and is therefore an effective way to fight unemployment.It lowers the costs of many services: without advertisements your daily newspaper would cost four times as much, the price of your television license would need to be doubled, and travel by bus or tube would cost 20 per cent more. And perhaps most important of all, advertising provides a guarantee of reasonable value in the produc...\n\nQ: By the first sentence of the passage the author means that   _  .", "options": ["he understands the cost of advertising well", "advertising costs money like everything else", "it is worthwhile to spend money on advertising", "everyone knows advertising is money consuming"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 103, "question": "The United States is full of cars. There are still many families without cars, but some families have two or more. However, cars are used for more than pleasure. They are a necessary part of life. Cars are used for business. They are driven to offices and factories by workers who have no other way to get to their jobs. When salesmen are sent to different parts of the city, they have to drive in order to carry their products. Farmers have to drive into the city in order to get supplies. Sometimes small children must be driven to school. In some cities school buses are used only when children live more than a mile away from the school. When the children are too young to walk too far, their mothers take turns driving them to school. One mother drives on Mondays taking her own children and the...\n\nQ: The United States is filled with cars, but  _  .", "options": ["not every family has a car", "few families have two cars or even more", "every American has a car", "every family has a car"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 332, "question": "HK's Family Affair The 32nd Hong Kong Art Festival, to be held early next year, will be based on the theme of \"family\". The art festival, considered to be Asia's best, began in 1973. \"We hope that people from Beijing and from all over the world will go to Hong Kong to enjoy the multiple performances in our art festival,\"Douglas Gautier, the festival's management director, said in a press conference in the capital. In the 29 days of the festival, which runs from February 8 to March 7, 2004, the audience can choose from 111 performances of 51 programmes staged by 700 foreign performers, 450 local artists and 160 actors from the mainland. Programmes vary from classical music, jazz, world music, Western and Peking opera, drama and dance to outdoor spectaculars. The programmes include Beethoven...\n\nQ: According to the text, we do NOT have any information about   _  .", "options": ["who will perform on stage", "what programmes there will be", "when the 32nd Art Festival will be held", "which theatres will put on performances"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 494, "question": "Warm weather brought by El Nino has had mixed effects on animals in usually snowy places in North America, including New England, according to an Associated Press article. Some animals seem to benefit from having a chance to gather more food before winter, and from expending less energy in daily survival mode. Others, like snowshoe hares, are put at center stage in predators' view when they lack snow for disguising their white fur -- not a good thing for them, of course. Black bears, on the other hand, have been keeping busy gathering nuts and apples, when they would normally have settled into their winter homes by now. Vermont and Massachusetts officials have asked residents to wait till snow falls to take out their bird feeders for the sake of safety, the article said. \"We suggest waitin...\n\nQ: Why did the officials ask people to keep bird feeders until snow falls?", "options": ["They may disturb bears.", "There's no need to do so.", "To avoid attracting bears.", "For the safety of bears."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2115, "question": "The landmark success of herbal expert Tu Youyou, the first Chinese woman national to win a Nobel prize in science, hasaroused an extreme sense of national pride and hopes on the future of traditional Chinese medicine (TCM). Tu, born in 1930, shared the 2015 Nobel Prize for Physiology or Medicine with Irish-born William Campbell and Japan's Satoshi Omura for her discoveries concerning a therapy against malaria. She discovered Artemisinin , a drug that has significantly reduced thedeath rates for patients suffering from malaria . \"Artemisinin is a gift for the world people from the traditional Chinese medicine. It is of great importance for curing malaria and other infectious diseases and for protecting the health of the world people,\" Tu said in Beijing. \"The discovery of Artemisinin is a s...\n\nQ: What type of writing is this text?   _", "options": ["An advertisement", "An announcement", "A speech", "A report"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1786, "question": "Here is some must-know information from a handbook on how people behave in doing business in some countries. In Brazil Brazilians are warm and friendly.They often stand close when talking and it is common for them to touch the person on the shoulder.People often greet each other (particularly women)with light cheek kisses . Schedules tend to be flexible,with business meetings sometimes starting later than planned.But to be safe,be on time.Meals can stretch for hours--there's no such thing as rushing a meal in Brazil.Lunches also can start in the mid to late afternoon.Brazilians are social,preferring face-to-face communication over emails or phone calls. In Singapore Singaporeans shake hands when they meet and often also greet each other with a small,polite bow.Business cards should be offe...\n\nQ: Why do Singaporeans avoid arguing with their boss?", "options": ["They put efficiency in the first place.", "They dislike face-to-face communication.", "They want to finish meetings as quickly as possible.", "They are supposed to obey the person of a higher rank."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1656, "question": "There is an English saying: \"Laughter is best medicine.\" Until recently, few people took the saying seriously. Now, however, doctors have begun to look into laughter and the effects it has on the human body. They have found that laughter really can improve people's health. Tests were carried out to study the effects of laughter on the body. People watched funny films while doctors checked their heart, blood pressure, breathing and muscles. It was found that laughter has similar effects to physical exercises. It increases blood pressure, the heart beating and breathing. It also works several groups of muscles in the face, the stomach, and even the feet. If laughter exercises the body, it must be beneficial. Other tests have shown that laughter appears to be able to reduce the effect of pain...\n\nQ: The main idea of the passage is   _  .", "options": ["laughter and physical exercises have similar effects.", "smile can produce the same effects as laughter", "pain can be reduced by laughter", "laughter is best medicine"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2945, "question": "Johnson went to Penquay for the weekend. He arrived there late on Friday evening. The landlady of the guest house, Mrs. Smith, answered the door and showed him to his room. Johnson was very tired and went straight to bed. He slept well and didn't wake up until nine o'clock the next morning. Johnson went downstairs for breakfast. Because there were no other guests, Mrs. Smith invited him to have breakfast with her family. Her only daughter, Catherine, about 13, was already sitting in the dining-room. Mrs. Smith went to the kitchen to prepare breakfast. Johnson noticed there were four places at the table and asked Catherine if there was another guest. Catherine told him that it was an empty place. And it used to be her father's place. Her father had been a fisherman. Three years before he ha...\n\nQ: What does the word \"scared\" probably mean?", "options": ["Excited.", "Upset.", "Frightened.", "Calm."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2972, "question": "My father, at the death of his father, was six years old, and he grew up without education. He moved from Kentucky to Indiana when I was seven. We reached our new home about the time the state came into the Union. It was a wild area, with many bears and other wild animals still in the woods. I grew up there. There were some so-called schools, but what was required of a teacher never went beyond \"reading, writing, and adding.\" If a stranger supposed to understand Latin happened to live for a time in the area, he was looked on as wizard . There was simply nothing to excite a desire for education. Of course, when I grew up, I did not know much. Still, somehow, I could read, write, and add, but that was all. The advance I have now made is on this store of education, which I have picked up unde...\n\nQ: The schools in the area   _  .", "options": ["were of poor quality", "offered all kinds of subjects", "respected those who knew Latin", "had teachers good at reading, writing, and adding"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 7, "question": "Little Tommy was doing very badly in math. His parents had tried everything--tutors, cards, special learning centers--in short, everything they could think of. Finally they took Tommy to a catholic school. After the first day, little Tommy came home with a very serious look on his face. He didn't kiss his mother hello. Instead, he went straight to his room and started studying. Books and papers were spread out all over the room and little Tommy was hard at work. His mother was surprised. She called him down to dinner and as soon as he finished eating, he went back to his room, without a word. In no time he was back hitting the books as hard as before. This went on for some time, day after day while the mother tried to understand what was happening. Finally, little Tommy brought home his re...\n\nQ: Tommy's mother felt surprised that his son  _  .", "options": ["was still the same as usual", "ate so much at dinner", "kissed her hello after school", "worked hard but said little"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1148, "question": "Planning to go to a gym? If you are one of those who have spent many days planning to join a gym or to attend it regularly, then why not choose some home exercise? Here are some home exercises without equipment. Jumping jacks This one is the best home workout without weights which is a great exercise that will work your hands and legs. Perform this exercise by standing with your feet placed together and arms at your sides. Now tuck in your abs and jump by bending in your knees. At the same time, move your feet apart as much as you can and raise your hands to bring in line with your shoulder. While you come back you must be in a starting position, feet together, hands at sides and knees bent. You must land on your heels and again jump. Jogging Jogging is one of the best home exercises witho...\n\nQ: To carry out jumping jacks effectively, you  _  .", "options": ["need to keep your two feet apart at first.", "must stand straight first and bend your abs.", "must use your arms to support your body.", "need to use your heels to touch the ground."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 17, "question": "A girl with blue eyes is a blue-eyed girl. A man with long legs is a long-legged man. A woman with white hair is a white-haired woman. Children who have good looks are good-looking children. What do you do when you want to buy clothes? You go to a shop. If you can find clothes that are the right size for you, and if they are ready to wear, you will probably buy them. They are called ready-made clothes. If you can not find clothes that are the right size, you will go to a tailor's shop. A tailor is a man who makes clothes. He will measure you carefully and will then make clothes for you. Such clothes are called tailor-made clothes. What do we call a man who is dressed badly? We call him a badly-dressed man. A woman who is dressed well is called a well-dressed woman. What do you wear when it...\n\nQ: 57. On back of a watch we can often see the word \"water-proof\". The word means_.", "options": ["water won't get into the watch", "you can put water into the watch", "not putting the watch into water", "you can see the watch clearly in water"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2889, "question": "A month after Hurricane Katrina, I returned home in New Orleans. There lay my house, reduced towaist-high ruins, smelly and dirty. Before the trip, I'd had my car fixed. When the office employee of the garage was writing up the bill,she noticed my Louisiana license plate. \"You from New Orleans?\"she asked I said I was, \"No charge.\"She said, and firmly shook her head when I reached for my wallet. The next day I went for a haircut, and the same thing happened. As my wife was studying in Florida, we decided to move there and tried to find a rental house that we could afford while also paying off a mortgage (> on our mined house. We looked at many places, but none was satisfactory. We'd began to accept that we*d have to live in extremely reduced circumstances for a while, when I got a very curi...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the text that  _", "options": ["the author's family was in financial difficulty", "rents were comparatively reasonable despite the disaster", "houses were difficult to find in the hurricane-stricken area", "the mortgage on the ruined house was paid off by the bank"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1864, "question": "My father always told me never to ever reveal my true opinions towards other people unless such opinions are positive. He said this is the \"Chu Shi Zhe Xue\", the philosophy of dealing with social network. It seems that everybody here just follows this philosophy very, very well. I would say that if I were given true friendship I would definitely treasure it with my greatest care. If I really regard someone as my close friend, I would never leave her alone whenever she's in need, either financially or mentally. And I always believe, as long as I treat people with whole-hearted honesty, I would have some rewards--at least, just ONE true friend of the same gender. Sometimes I just miss my friends in China. Perhaps when we became friends, we were still young, too young to have been polluted by...\n\nQ: What do we know about the writer's father according to this passage?", "options": ["He is really a good philosopher.", "He can get on well with others.", "He told the writer to reveal her true opinions.", "The passage doesn't mention it."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 529, "question": "Are you having too much salt? You might not think so, but people in China eat on average about 12 grams of salt each day, that is much higher than the 6 grams suggested by the World Health Organization. You could be eating too much without realizing it, because about 75% of the salt we eat is already in the food we buy, such as bread, sauces, soups and sausages. What problems can eating too much salt cause? To answer that question, first let's take a look at what salt is. Salt is a chemical compound. It is made of sodium and chloride . Salt is used to keep and flavor foods. A small amount of salt is important for good health because our bodies need sodium and chloride to work. But past studies have found that people who eat more salt than they need tend to have high blood pressure. Eating ...\n\nQ: What is the purpose of the article?", "options": ["To warn people of food containing too much salt.", "To inform people of the right amount of salt taken each day.", "To advise people to be careful about the amount of salt they eat.", "To promote the right way to make reduced salt food."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2478, "question": "The United Nations says forty million people or so around the world went hungry in 2008, mainly because of higher food prices. Early estimates from the UN Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) show that 963 million people did not get enough to eat. World food prices have dropped since early 2008. Prices of major crops have decreased by more than half from their height earlier last year. But they remain high compared to earlier years. But FAO official Hafez Ghanem says lower prices have failed to end the food crisis in many poor countries. \"For millions in developing countries,\" he says, \"getting enough food every day to live an active and healthy life is a distant dream.\" The FAO says food shortage is a threat to people's health. Today, two-thirds of the world's _ people live in just a f...\n\nQ: What is the best title of this passage?", "options": ["The food production of the world", "The hunger reduction target of the FAO", "The food shortage around the world", "The solution to the global food shortage"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1933, "question": "Among professional basketball players,Jeremy Lin's background is not typical.He graduated from Harvard University,which sends few players to the NBA,and he is the only ChineseAmerican NBA player.But when you watch him on the court,there is no doubt that he belongs there.He moves with speed and grace that show years of faithful practice,which is fueled by a love for basketball. The Family Effect Lin's enjoyment of basketball actually began in Taiwan,where his father started watching it.Lin's father moved to U.S.,and his interest in the sport only grew.He passed on this love of basketball to his son,introducing him to the game at the age of five.The young Lin spent much of his youth playing basketball for fun.After each game,his parents would discuss not only his score but also his conduct t...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the text?", "options": ["What Is Next for Jeremy Lin?", "Jeremy Lin's Tips for Success", "Following Dreams and Finding Joy", "Six NBA Teams Eyeing Jeremy Lin"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 440, "question": "You could feel sorry for Alberto Torres, who is blind. The last thing he remembers seeing was his daughter being born 13 years ago. Then the world went blank; he can only imagine what his only child looks like now, as a teenaged honor student. Bad luck is no stranger to this warm and thoughtful 37-year-old man. His mother died of cancer when he was 4, and his father, who was often ill, had to give him up to the care of the state when he was 11. He later worked for 19 years in a workshop making household goods, deathly boring work. Earlier this month, Alberto Torres's wife, who had just been laid off from her job, had to have a breast removed due to cancer and now faces a year of radiation treatments. Things seemed always to go from almost incredibly bad to worse. Even Mr. Torres's good luc...\n\nQ: The description of Mr. Torres's long trip to work shows   _  .", "options": ["the effective traffic system", "the kindness of New Yorkers", "the loyalty of his guide dog", "his will to overcome difficulty"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1610, "question": "November not only marks the publication of Toni Morrison's eagerly anticipated eighth novel, Love, but it is also the tenth anniversary of her Nobel Prize for Literature. Morrison is the first black woman to receive a Nobel, and so honored before her in literature are only two black men:Wole Soyinka, the Nigerian playwright, poet and novelist, in 1986; and Derek Walcott, the Caribbean-born poet, in 1992. But Morrison is also the first and only American-born Nobel prizewinner for literature since 1962, the year novelist John Steinbeck received the award. Like Song of Solomon, Love is a multigenerational story, revealing the personal and communal Legacy of an outstanding black family. As Morrison scholars will tell you, Love is the third volume of a literary master's trilogy investigating th...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the text?", "options": ["Toni Morrison's latest novels", "Toni Morrison and her trilogy", "Toni Morrison and her novel Love", "Toni Morrison, the Nobel prizewinner"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3200, "question": "Climate change has been blamed for killer hurricanes, sea level rise, and drought, but a new report suggests the effects of climate change might hit the world's coffee supply. Up to 70 percent of the world's coffee supply could be threatened over the next 66 years, according to a new study by researchers at England's Royal Botanic Gardens. Nearly 100 percent of the world's Arabica coffee growing regions could become unsuitable for the plant by 2080, according to the study. Beans from Arabica coffee plants account for about 70 percent of the world's coffee, but the plant also has to be grown under strict weather conditions: they grow well at temperatures between 64 and 70 degrees Celsius, and are highly influenced by frost or temperatures higher than 73 degrees Celsius. With temperatures es...\n\nQ: In order to solve the problem of Arabica, coffee plants, some farmers_.", "options": ["would make efforts to produce high-quality coffee.", "would bring in artificial cooling techniques.", "would tend to move to some warm places.", "would grow more wild Arabica."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1580, "question": "On a hot summer day, a soft drink can really take away your thirst. At home, at school, in the park or at the movies---you can find one almost anywhere. Carbonated You can see bubbles in these! Of all soft drinks sold, about 75 percent are carbonated . But be careful, carbonated soft drinks have lots of sugar and caffeine . Caffeine is not very good for you in the summer because it takes water out of your body. And the sugar can make you overweight if you drink too much. Fruit juice There are different kinds of juice. One kind is made only from fresh fruit. This kind of fruit juice may not taste sweet enough for some people, but it is nutritious . Another kind of fruit juice tastes good but has lots of sugar in it. Many young people buy this kind because the advertisements are good. It is ...\n\nQ: After sports, you have sports drinks because  _  .", "options": ["they can take away your thirst", "they can put back minerals you've lost in sweat", "they have funny names that sound very exciting", "they have no sugar"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1946, "question": "Artie Shaw was born in New York City in 1910. His name was Arthur Arshawsky. His parents were poor immigrants who had come to the United States from Eastern Europe. His family later moved to New Haven, Connecticut. At the age of fourteen, he began to play the saxophone and then the clarinet. From a very young age, Artie Shaw wanted to play his clarinet better than anyone. He wanted his sound and music to be perfect. He worked at this task much of his life. He began working as a professional musician when he was fifteen. He left home and began playing in bands across the United States. In 1928, young Artie Shaw traveled to Chicago, Illinois to hear the great trumpet player, Louis Armstrong. He immediately understood that Armstrong's great jazz sound was the beginning of something new and ex...\n\nQ: When Artie Shaw became an adult,    _   .", "options": ["he showed a growing interest in jazz music", "he worked for Columbia Broadcast System radio network as a singer", "he formed a small band when he was twenty three", "he thought that racial separation should be the rule of the society"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1851, "question": "Depressed people can be very difficult to be around,and yet they need more than the usual amount of support and understanding from their friends and family. The anger and lack of concern that a depressed person may have for people close to him or her can be very disturbing to someone who's trying to help.At such times,the sincerity of a friend or a family member is questioned when the depressed person doesn't feel worthy of someone's friendship.Withdrawal from others can make it nearly impossible to encourage a depressed person to enter into activities that may help pull him or her out of the depression. It is frequently difficult for a depressed person to carry on a conversation.Attempts to help may be met with defensiveness and verbal attacks.While being supportive and understanding,the ...\n\nQ: Too much \"doing for\" can   _  .", "options": ["cause more severe depression", "give the depressed person courage", "result in defensiveness from the depressed person", "be of no help to the depressed person"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2597, "question": "Parties held by the wealthy seldom welcome poor guests.But last week China made it through the doors into a gathering of the world's richest countries. Jin Renqing ,Chian's finance minister,and Zhou Xiaochuan,governor of the People's Bank of China,joined a meeting of the Group of Seven(G7)on October1,2004.It is the fist time that China has had direct talks with the club.It was a good chance to share the world powers'thoughts about critical economic issues and _ understanding. China'a participation is a natural part of its increasingly important role in the global economy.China is the world 's factory and the biggest market. America and China made up almost half of global economic growth last year.\"If Anerican consumers and Chinese producers were to reduce their activities at the same time,...\n\nQ: From the passage we can infer that   _  .", "options": ["Chinese producers as well as American consumers contribute a lot to the growth of the world economy", "the author doesn't think it necessary for China to participate in the meeting", "China produces a lot but consumes a little", "the economist thinks that American consumers and Chinese producers will reduce their activitres at the same time"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1464, "question": "I have only once been in trouble with the law.The whole process of being arrested and taken to court was a rather unpleasant experience at the time, but it makes a good story now. What makes it rather disturbing was the arbitrary circumstances both of my arrest and my subsequent fate in court. It happened in February about twelve years ago.I had left school a couple of months before that and was not due to go to university until the following October.I was still living at home at the time. One morning I was in Richmond, a suburb of London near where I lived.I was looking for a temporary job so that I could save up some money to go traveling.As it was a fine day and I was in no hurry, I was taking my time, looking in shop windows, strolling in the park, and sometimes just stopping and looki...\n\nQ: The author believes that he would most probably have been declared guilty if   _  .", "options": ["the magistrate had been less gentle", "he had really been out of work", "he had been born in a lower--class family", "both B and C"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2715, "question": "The Sunset Pasta Cruise to Emerald Bay Saturday evening, September 25, 2010 You will cruise to Emerald Bay at Sunset, one of the most beautiful places in the world while dining on a Pasta Buffet and listening to live light dance music. Buses will pick up Sunset Pasta Cruise diners from the main entrance to the Horizon Casino Resort at: 4:40pm and 5:05pm on Saturday and take you the 1.5 miles to Ski Run Marina for boarding. Boarding is at Ski Run Marina at 5:15 p.m. (with departure at 5:45 p.m.), located in South Lake Tahoe. The cost for the cruise, pasta buffet, live music, and the 2.5-hour cruise to Emerald Bay is $55 (normally $75). The cost for children between 3-11 is $41 and under 3 is free. Must register the under 3 as well for the coast guard count. The Sunset Pasta Cruise will be l...\n\nQ: How much will Mrs. Robert and her 15-year-old son pay for the cruise?", "options": ["$96.", "$110.", "$116.", "$150."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1331, "question": "Jogging has become the most popular individual sport in America. Many theories,even some mystical ones,have been advanced to explain the popularity of jogging. The plain truth is that jogging is a cheap,quick and efficient way to maintain (or achieve) physical fitness. The most useful sort of exercise is exercise that develops the heart,lungs, and circulatory systems. If these systems are fit,the body is ready for almost any sport and for almost any sudden demand made by work or emergencies. One can train more specifically,as by developing strength for weight lifting or the ability to run straight ahead for short distances with great power as in football,but running trains your heart and lungs to deliver oxygen more efficiently to all parts of your body. It is worth doing that: this sort o...\n\nQ: We can conclude from this passage that   _  ..", "options": ["jogging makes heart disease no longer be an American problem", "jogging can be harmful if the runner is not properly prepared", "suits are preferable to gym shoes and T-shirts", "jogging is bad for the ankles and knees"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1809, "question": "Humans may be a bad influence on their best friends---at least when it comes to problem-solving. In a task that wasn't very tough, wolves performed must better than dogs. All the animals had to do was pull the lid off a food container, containing a sausage treat. Monique Udell studies animal behavior at Oregon State University in Corvallis. She tested 10 pet dogs and another 10 dogs from an animal shelter. In one set of tests, a person was nearby but did not encourage or discourage the dogs. Those dogs typically spent 10 to 15 percent of their time gazing at the person. They spent a mere 5 percent of their time or less touching the container. Udell offered the same challenge to wolves. These animals had been raised and fed by people but still lived outdoors. Here, the wolves didn't look at...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the text?", "options": ["How wolves and dogs differ from each other", "The reason why wolves are dangerous", "Dogs are more relaxed when no one is around", "Wolves beat dogs in problem-solving tests"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2820, "question": "When someone meets a stranger with the same hobby, that person immediately becomes a friend. People enjoy the company of others who share a similar interest. Often they will form a club and travel great distances to attend meetings where they can talk about their hobbies. Other people have such unusual hobbies that no one else can share them. Sometimes they try to do something better, faster or longer than anyone else in order to have their names included in the Guinness Book of World Records. A lady in Massachusetts may have the world's easiest hobby; she let her hair grow. Diane Witt has not cut her hair for twelve years. It is now eight feet (2.44 meters) long, and she will soon set a new world record and her name will be placed in the Guinness Book. A thirty-year-old man in Pennsylvani...\n\nQ: How many persons are mentioned about breaking world records in the passage?", "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1171, "question": "Computer power is moving into the \"cloud\"--networks of data centres that use the Internet to supply all kinds of services, from e-mail and social networks to data storage and analysis. The rise of cloud computing is rapid and causing huge changes in the tech industry. The old guard is suffering: this week's $67 billion merger between Dell and EMC, makers of computers and storage devices respectively , was a marriage forced by the rise of the cloud. Disruptive newcomers are blooming: if Amazon's cloud-computing unit were a stand-alone public company, it would probably be worth almost as much as Dell and EMC combined. The gains for customers have been equally dramatic. Compared with older IT systems, cloud computing is often much cheaper. It adds tremendous flexibility: firms that need more ...\n\nQ: With wide applications of cloud computing customers can   _  .", "options": ["pay less for the older IT systems", "gain more computing capacity quickly", "know better about defeating the hackers", "install software within weeks"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 635, "question": "When people who are nature lovers worldwide wish all humans to realize the importance of their natural surroundings, many Australians are turning caring for the environment into a way of life. Julie, an Australian housewife in Brisbane is one such example. Even though autumn is approaching Australia's Brisbane in April, one can still watch colorful blooming flowers in Julie's little garden, as she tells that in her community,\"Each of us has a beautiful yard. The whole community, from children to elderly people, takes care of the environment as if they are taking care of their own garden.\" \"Gardening is the most popular club in our community,\" she says. \"A lot of retired people don't just regularly organize gardening lectures, but also personally visit families in the community to provide g...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the text?", "options": ["How Australians save resources", "Love nature, the Australian way", "How Australians lead their life", "Protect nature, a must of life"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 155, "question": "It is well known that Einstein was the father of the famous Theory of Relativity. But do you know it owes a great deal to Marits, Einstein's former wife? In 1896, 17-year-old Einstein went to Zurich to study physics. There he met a girl from Hungary. They studied in the same class. The same interest brought the two together and the young man fell in love with Marits. In 1903, when Einstein was 24 years old, he married Marits, who was 4 years older than he. After their marriage, Einstein devoted himself to the research of the great theory. To give her husband more help, Marits gave up her own work, and became a good wife and assistant. She tried her best to encourage him whenever possible and she was sure that her husband would succeed. They often discussed the theory while walking outside ...\n\nQ: By the year of 1914, Einstein had   _  .", "options": ["become famous all over the world", "been proud of his success", "suffered from the 1st World War", "lost touch with Marits"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2484, "question": "A good friend of mine was complaining about her son the other day.\"Did you notice,\" she started, \"how he didn't wait for me to get my salad before he dove into his?\" True enough, the boy attacked his plate faster than a cat in the wild.Without manners, we're no more than animals.Actually, that's not true.I've been watching and feeding a group of wild cats, and they show unusual politeness toward each other.Even when food is _ , they take turns, leaving at least a small part for the next in line. My mother educated her three children to have good manners all the time.We were made to feel very uncomfortable as if we were sitting on pins and needles until we got used to saying please, thank you, pardon me, and I'm sorry.And I have to say, while it was a painful learning experience, it was one...\n\nQ: What did the writer's friend most probably complain about?", "options": ["Her son's eating too quickly.", "Her son's not having a healthy diet.", "Her son's not having good table manners.", "Teenagers' not having good manners."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 522, "question": "A recent online poll asked kids what they hated most about school. \"Classes are boring\" came in first. \"Too much homework\" was a close second. Since all activities remain interesting for only so long, too much homework can lead to ennui. So, why are some kids getting homework overload? Teachers give two reasons. First, they say, the government now requires schools to meet higher-than-ever achievement goals for students. If students don' t succeed, the school faces punishment. Second, many parents want their children to be able to get into the best colleges and universities. These parents believe homework is a way to ensure that students are learning as much as possible. People who favor homework argue that it can have many beneficial effects. They claim it can help students develop good st...\n\nQ: The author's purpose in writing the passage is   _  .", "options": ["to criticize the school teachers", "to attract public attention to kids' study", "to offer more help to today's kids", "to call for proper amounts of homework"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1712, "question": "It's a warm summer afternoon. You're cooking up the catch of the day over a campfire. Suddenly, a few raindrops fall on your arms, and before you know it, the sky is opened up. Then you hear what sounds like thunder in the distance. What should you do? Your tent is close by and would offer shelter from the pouring rain. There's a campsite picnic shelter a few minutes down the path. And then you remember that your car is parked down the road. What's your safest choice to make sure you and your families are safe? It's a common question for many hikers and campers, especially when they are camping during summer months. Heading to your car is almost always the safest choice. Your tent and a picnic shelter will keep you dry, but they offer little or no protection against lightening. Your car, o...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE?", "options": ["Campers like car camping best.", "Young people like backpacking best.", "Lightening is a danger for campers.", "Camping during summer months is the most popular."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1675, "question": "Thanks a Million, Dad I was born disabled.A difficult birth, feet first, my head stuck.By my first birthday, I couldn't stand or walk. When I was three, the doctor told dad I had cerebral palsy .A loss of oxygen to my brain had destroyed brain signals to the right side of my body. But no son of my dad' s was going to be disabled.Every morning before breakfast and every evening before bed, my dad placed me on the bedroom floor to exercise my right leg.The muscles were shrunk and twisted together.Back and forth up and down, my dad pushed and pulled the muscles into shape. But my dad' s exercise of passion didn't stop there.For my 13th birthday, he threw me a special party.When everybody was gone, he brought me to open a large box, it was a-set of boxing gloves.We put them on.My dad kept on b...\n\nQ: What do we learn from the passage?", "options": ["The author has a talent for boxing.", "The author achieved a lot thanks to his father' s love.", "The author became a baseball star with the help of his father.", "The author doesn't think his father should be so strict with him."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1763, "question": "Up, Up, and Away! An adventurer who became the first person to fly across the English Channel on a cluster of balloons has launched a house into the sky just like in the hit movie Up-in reparation for a more ambitious journey and a new record Fearless Trappe , from North Carolina, stepped into the cartoon themed home before flying above the leon International Balloon Festivel in Mexico more than a week ago. The 38-year-old Trappe was using the event as a warm-up for his planned trans-Atlantic flight scheduled for next summer ,He aims to complete the 2,500-mile journey in a seven-foot lifeboat carried by 365 huge helium ballooms The brave man is learning to sail a lifeboat ,in case he meeds to ditch into the ocean during the danger-filled adventure He sill fly at between 18,000 feet and 25,...\n\nQ: To finish the journey ,he will fly a distance of  _", "options": ["2500 miles", "18,000 feet", "25,000 feet", "230 miles"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3325, "question": "Phyllis Lee of prefix = st1 /Singaporeknew something wasn't right. Her younger son, Alex, then six years old, was getting good grades in his private kindergarten classes. But Lee realized something was wrong when Alex came home one day, crying, with \"zeroes\" on his Chinese spelling test. Lee decided to investigate. According to Lee, the teacher would frequently describe Alex's Chinese writing as 'ghost writings' and made him a laughing stock in class instead of helping him out. Lee, 46, spent the next 12 months teaching Alex and still helps him when necessary. She not only taught him the formation of the Chinese words but also their origin so that he could understand better, often taking more than an hour to read a simple paragraph. Visits to the library and surfing the Internet kept her u...\n\nQ: Lee's education method succeeds mainly because of her_.", "options": ["involvement", "communication", "tolerance", "encouragement"], "answer": 0}]